FARIBORZ KOREVLI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I'm a Vue front-end developer with experience in many frameworks and libraries like Quasar, Vuetify, Vuesax, Bootstrap Vue, Element UI, VueX, Pinia, Web3.js, and more. In my previous roles, I developed and maintained web applications using Vue 2, Vue 3, and web3.js in SPA, SSR, and PWA modes. I have experience working independently as well as part of a team, and I am comfortable collaborating with other team members and stakeholders to ensure that projects are completed on time and to a high standard.

Additionally, I am currently deepening my knowledge of ReactJs to expand my skill set and be a strong candidate for React projects.

EXPERIENCE

Head of Frontend

Allinso | October 2023 - April 2024

- Company Overview: All In (ALLIN) is an Al-centric initiative on the Ethereum blockchain, dedicated to empowering communities and businesses. Provides solutions in data analysis, process automation, customer service, community management, and content development
- Implemented Allin Al and Allbuys Telegram web apps using Vue 3, Quasar, Pinia, Vite, and telegram-web-app.js

Frontend Developer

Freelance | November 2021 - October 2022

- Implemented Web3 NFT Minting Apps and Token Gate Solution for https://www.minth.io (Web3 JS & Moralis & Webflow)
- Implemented https://ascendants-sample.web.app NFT web app and https://web3-sample-test.web.app NFT minting test app (Web3 JS & Vue 3 & Quasar & Pinia)
- Provided consultation to a Romanian business on their issues, built their project structure (Vue 2 & Quasar & Vuesax & VueX & PWA), and provided solutions to make their UI more intuitive

Frontend Team Lead

Bidar Brokerage | Tehran | December 2019 - March 2020

- Company Overview: EghtesadBidar Brokerage Company, A leading Iranian brokerage firm established in 2004, is recognized for its "A" rating from the Stock Exchange and is dedicated to providing innovative financial solutions
- **For 4 months, at the same time with Saman Salamat Pajoh (In coordination with the managers of both companies)
- Implemented the registration system of the Eghtesad Bidar Brokerage (Vue 2 & BootstrapVue & VueX)
- Implemented the "Sabad gardaan" website of the Eghtesad Bidar Brokerage (Nuxt & BootstrapVue)
- Trained junior developers

CONTACT

- **4** +989226206718
- fariborzkorevli@gmail.com
- Alborz, Iran
- firibz.com
- t.me/firibz
- bit.ly/firibz-skype

SKILLS

- Vue.js (Vue 2, Vue 3)
- · React.is
- web3.js
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS
- Telegram mini apps
- Quasar Framework, Bootstrap Vue, Vuetify, Element Ui, Vuesax
- · Composition API, Options API
- · SPA, PWA, SSR
- · Vite, Webpack
- Pinia, VueX
- Lottie
- · Selenium, C#
- · Git, TFS

EDUCATION

Master's degree

E-Commerce/Electronic Commerce Islamic Azad University E-Campus October 2024

Bachelor's degree

Information Technology Semnan University January 2017

Frontend Developer

Saman Salamat Pajouh | Tehran | November 2017 - April 2023

- Company Overview: Saman Salamat Pajoh implements and maintains Iran Food and Drug Administration (IRFDA) systems
- Worked on more than 10 national projects with millions of users
- Designed and implemented a new front-end structure based on Vue 3 composition API, Quasar, and Vite for the next generation of systems to make them faster and lighter and improve their UI and UX, also enhanced the development and maintenance process significantly
- Led the migration of several projects from AngularJS to Vue, making them about 19x lighter and extremely faster, with big improvements in UI and UX. including the Supply Chain Management System (Vue 3 & Quasar & Pinia), Adverse Drug Reaction (ADR) Systems (including Management system, Reporter system, and Reports system) (Vue 2 & Quasar & VueX & PWA), and Identity Provider (IDP) System (Vue 2 & Vuetify)
- Trained developers and people interested in front-end development
- Interviewed candidates for the front-end developer and test engineer positions
- Implemented the new Labeling system (Vue 3 & Quasar & Pinia & Vite) and Covid-19 Effective Drugs Supply Management System (Vue 2 & Quasar)
- Worked as a front-end Developer on many AngularJS systems
- Worked as an automation test engineer(Selenium, NUnit, Extent reports, Specflow,...)
 and QA test engineer on several projects

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- firibz.com
- linkedin.com/in/firibz
- stackoverflow.com/users/8755786/fariborz-korevli
- github.com/firibz